https://elocpa.com/privacy-policy

ELO CPAs & Advisors | Website Privacy Policy
This site requires JavaScript and you do not have it enabled. You may find that many things on the site don't work, including all submission forms. Please enable JavaScript.
Skip to content
About ELO
Leadership
Accountants
Accounting Support
Administrative
Services
Auditing & Attestation
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Certain functions on our website require us to collect personal data from our users in order to do general business. Examples of personal data collected include (but not limited to) name, phone number, email address, physical and/or mailing address information. Information such as this is necessary to provide our website visitors with quotes for insurance products and respond to correspondence initiated through our insurance quote and contact forms. When you initiate contact with ELO CPAs and Advisors through filling out the Contact form on our website or submit information through our online forms, your consent for collection and retention of this information for normal business usage is implied.
Embedded content from other websites
Content on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, links, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Information about our website visitors is also collected through the use of Google Analytics. That software collects information about our visitors such as pages visited, duration of time on site, browser and general device information, etc. We use these statistical tools to analyze our website’s usefulness to our visitors and make improvements when needed. Google’s privacy policy can be found here.
Cookies
In order to provide our website visitors with a more customized experience, we have included an option for you to select a community. When you select a community, a cookie with this selection is saved in your browser. The cookie is used to customize the news and events listings shown on the page. This cookie expires after 1 day.
Who we share your data with
Information, as described above, is collected for ELO’s business needs. We do not share or sell your contact information with any third parties. We partner with Insight Marketing Design to host and maintain our website, and as such, they have full access to information collected and stored through our website. This partnership is necessary to maintain and improve our website services. Website administrators also have full access to data collected and stored by ELO’s website.
How long we retain your data
Data collected, as described above, is retained indefinitely for customer service purposes and as storage space allows.
What rights you have over your data
If you have submitted any forms on this website, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Data related to our website is held on a secured web server in the USA
Our contact information
Privacy-specific concerns can be sent to:
ELO CPAs & Advisors
Mitchell Office
1820 N Sanborn Blvd
PO Box 249
Mitchell, SD 57301
605.996.7717
Additional information
How we protect your data
Our hosting company uses a secure firewall to keep out unauthorized users and ensure the integrity of our systems. We are vigilant about protecting our site from unwanted intrusions.
ELO CPA Locations
Mitchell Office
1820 N Sanborn BlvdPO Box 249Mitchell, SD 57301
605-996-7717Sioux Falls Office
5000 S. Broadband Lane, Ste 119Sioux Falls, SD 57108
605-271-1302Yankton Office
118 W 3rd StYankton, SD 57078
605-665-6007Huron Office
©2020 ELO Prof, LLC. All rights reserved.
Business to Consumer Industry website design and programming by insight marketing design
